# Oluwakayode Babalola

## **Content Writer**

9, Oyinlola Street, Baruwa, Lagos. +234 810-435-9615 babalolakayode44@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

Content and copywriter with more than two years experience creating content for businesses of all sizes. Adept in researching, writing, editing, and proofreading engaging and SEO-friendly content such as website copy, blog articles, promotional emails, product descriptions, and other copy. Experienced with content management systems, knowledge of SEO principles, web design, and web usability.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

PRJXT 22:29, Lagos, Nigeria- Copywriter / Creative Writer

**DECEMBER 2022 - PRESENT** 

- Write and edit content for brand website
- Create marketing materials for brand identity and exposure
- Implement SEO best practices and write website copy that is in line with client goals and brand.
- Work with clients to understand their brand, values, and objectives.
- Develop creative brief documents that are in line with the identity the client is trying to display
- Create Brand Identity / Brand Decks for artistes or brands

Jetron Ticket, Lagos, Nigeria- Senior Content Writer

**DECEMBER 2021 - PRESENT** 

- Published blog content about entertainment resulting in an increase in monthly visitors.
- Optimized old website content with up-to-date SEO guidelines and increased traffic by 15%
- Proof-read submitted articles and made necessary change before publishing
- Created promotional email copies to increase brand visibility

#### **EDUCATION**

Ajayi Crowther University- B.Sc Computer Science

**SEPTEMBER 2018 - JULY 2022** 

GPA: 4.06/5.0

## **SKILLS**

SEO Research, Creative Writing, Blogging, Email Marketing, Research and Fact-checking, Script Writing, Communication, Teamwork, Time Management, Problem Solving, Remote Work

### **INTEREST**

• Running a blog named LOCALITY (https://localmanwt.blogspot.com/) highlighting the challenges creatives struggle with